export const pythonNestedConditionsExercise = {
  title: 'Python Nested Conditions â€“ Exercise',
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'Nested condition means?',
      options: [
        'Loop inside loop',
        'If inside if',
        'Function inside function',
        'Loop inside if',
      ],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'Which keyword is used to check another condition?',
      options: ['else', 'elif', 'for', 'while'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'Inner if executes when?',
      options: [
        'Outer if is false',
        'Outer if is true',
        'Always',
        'Never',
      ],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'Which avoids deep nesting?',
      options: ['if', 'else', 'elif', 'pass'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'Nested conditions are mainly used for?',
      options: [
        'Iteration',
        'Decision making',
        'Input',
        'Output',
      ],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: 'Which is mandatory in nested conditions?',
      options: ['Brackets', 'Semicolon', 'Indentation', 'Comma'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: 'Which statement executes when all conditions are false?',
      options: ['if', 'elif', 'else', 'pass'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: 'Nested if can exist inside?',
      options: ['if only', 'else only', 'elif only', 'All'],
      correctIndex: 3,
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'Which improves readability over deep nesting?',
      options: ['elif', 'break', 'continue', 'pass'],
      correctIndex: 0,
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'Nested conditions help in solving?',
      options: [
        'Single condition problems',
        'Complex logic problems',
        'Loops only',
        'Functions only',
      ],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
  ],
}